{
    "question": "Ubah kalimat tersebut ke dalam bentuk pasif    1. It is said that many people are homeless after floods\r\n2. People say that Arthur is very rich\r\n3. People say that he has 22 children\u00a0",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "1. It is said that many people are homeless after floods<br>-- ini udah pasif ya?\u00a0<br>Many people are homeless due to flood, it is said by the newspaper<br><br>2. People say that Arthur is very rich<br>Arthur is very rich, is said by people<br><span><br>3. People say that he has 22 children\u00a0<br>he has 22 children, is said by people\u00a0<br><br></span>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "bisa-gak-buatin-pidato-dari-teks-ini-plastic-surgery-is-not-s-r-624",
            "question": "Bisa gak buatin pidato dari teks ini\u00a0    plastic surgery is not s recent phenimenon, but it was appeared since 3000 years ago. in the past, it was for medical purpose but now it is creating beuty and trend to modify some part of body.\r\nmany people nowaday want to be extraordinary such as animal or less human by plastic surgery. they modifying their faces and bodies to make them more animal like. meny so called 'lizard people' have had their tongues split. a woman who changed her face like a cat. other people gone beyond different kinds of tattoos.\r\nthe people who done outcast actually they lack self respect and have adesperate need for attention. they should be treated by psychiatrist, not plastic surgeons. and we should be aware of society that no longer wants to look human",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "hi people, today i will tell you about plastic surgery. plastic surgery appeared 3000 years ago, in the past, it was for medical purpose but now it is only for a change of appearance. many people nowdays want to have a beautiful or handsome face, in other words &#039;being closer to perfections in the matter of appearance&#039;. but some people have some really weird tastes and they tried to be less human-like, by using plastic surgery, they tried to looks like a lizard or cats, and many other animals. the people that took plastic surgery is usually people who is not satisfied with their looks, or their body. they degraded\u00a0the gods creation, and try to be more &#039;perfect&#039;, however they sometime did not look at the risk. you see, if the surgery failed, then can you even imagine what your body or face would look like? and because of that i highly recommend not to take plastic surgery, and appreciate what god has given to us.\u00a0\u00a0<br><br>^aku tambahin beberapa informasi\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-the-word-darling-is-derived-from-an-old-english-term-meaning-251",
            "question": "1. The word \"Darling\" is derived from an old english term meaning \"Favorite Minion\" . Explain the positive and negative meaning of \"Darling\".    2. IBM is has laid of 20 percent of their workforce with a signature on a single piece of paper.\r\n\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 1\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 2\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 3\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 4\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 5\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 6\r\na. Find out the error option.\r\nb. Explain why it is wrong\r\n\r\nmohon bantuannya yaa..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. The word \"Darling\" is derived from an old English term meaning \"Favorite Minion\" . Explain the positive and negative meaning of \"Darling\".<br>Positive Meaning : It&#039;s a person that we concern as lovely and lovable, therefore we prioritize this darling as the first priority.<br>Negative : Since the word darling means favorite minion, it also trigger the feeling of possessiveness, that sometime it has negative effect on their freedom and privacy.\u00a0<br><br><span>2.\u00a0</span><u>IBM</u><span>\u00a0is\u00a0</span><u>has</u><span>\u00a0laid of\u00a0</span><u>20 percent</u><span>\u00a0of\u00a0</span><u>their</u>\u00a0<u>workforce</u><span>\u00a0with a signature on a\u00a0</span><u>single</u><span>\u00a0piece of paper.</span><br>\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 1\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 2\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 3\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 4\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 5\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 6<br>a. Find out the error option.<br><br>number 2 - &gt; should be<br>IBM has laid without &#039;is&#039;\u00a0<br>b. Explain why it is wrong<br>if we use Is, then it will have pasive meaning, which means that IBM get bankrupt due to their worker\u00a0<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "there-care-many-reasons-for-keeping-dogs-as-pete-in-the-city-area-554",
            "question": "There care many reasons for keeping dogs as Pete in the city area, but many peo- ple feel that keeping pet dogs should not be allowed In the city. Dogs are often not taken care properly. They are kept in small backyards and rarely taken for walks. They are left in the yard all day by themselves while the family rune work. Very little attention is given to the dog and it is not a very good life for it. It is no wonder why these dogs bark and disturb the neighbours and become a nuisance to the community.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 On the other hand, not all people treat their dogs this may and why should the peo- ple receive a lot of pleasure and enjoyment from dog's stifle'? Dogs can make a lonely person's life happy or make wonderful play- mate. It can also teach a child responsibility as they not only Potts lay with the dog, but also need to exercise, feed, and care for the dog.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 I feel that we should be allowed to keep dogs in the city, because ills is taken care of properly, dogs can be a great source of pleasure. As a child / used to enjoy playing and taking care of my pet. There is not greater loyalty a nelson can get than from a well-caned dog.\u00a0    1. Some people do not like the presence of pet dogs In their surroundings because ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are left in the yards\u00a0 \r\n(B) the dogs are often neglected \r\n(C) the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours \r\n(D) the dogs play with the owner's child \r\n(E) the dogs guard the security of the enyit onrnent\u00a0 \r\n\r\n2. The main idea of the last paragraph is ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) pet dogs are loyal animals \r\n(B) pet dogs are more loyal than humans \r\n(C) dogs can be a great source of pleasure \r\n(D) the writer has no objection to keeping dogs In the city \r\n(E) the writer used to play and took care of his pet when he was a child\u00a0 \r\n\r\n3. We can infer from the text that keeping pet dogs in the city will not cause any problem as long ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are amusing \r\n(B) the neighbours like having pet dogs \r\n(C) the dogs do not balk at the neighbours \r\n(D) the writer has succeeded in persuading the neighbours \r\n(E) its presence does not disturb the neighbourhood",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1.c.the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours<br>2.c.dogs can be a great source of pleasure<br>3.e.it&#039;s presence does not disturb the neighbourhood<br>ini menurut jawaban saya :)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-expressions-of-surprise-untuk-dua-orang-622",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan \"Expressions of surprise\" Untuk dua orang?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Dina : Hi dani did you know that everyone in this school is talking about you because\u00a0you are the winner of the sains olympiad?<br>Dani : Wow, what a surprise i can&#039;t believe it<br>Dina : Yeah you are the winner good job my friend<br>Dani : Thanks a lot dina<br>Dina : You&#039;re welcome dani",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "membuat-kalimat-simple-present-dengan-kata-yg-d-bawah-1know-2w-351",
            "question": "Membuat kalimat simple present dengan kata yg d bawah:    1.know\r\n2.write\r\n3.cut\r\n4.drive\r\n5.drink\r\n6.give\r\n7.become\r\n8.overcome\r\n9.keep\r\n10.set\r\n11.hang\r\n12.sing\r\n13.tell\r\n14.shoot\r\n15.grow\r\n16.meet\r\n17.undo\r\n18.feel\r\n19.cost\r\n20.come",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": ".know<br>2.write<br>3.cut<br>4.drive<br>5.drink<br>6.give<br>7.become<br>8.overcome<br>9.keep<br>10.set<br>11.hang<br>12.sing<br>13.tell<br>14.shoot<br>15.grow<br>16.meet<br>17.undo<br>18.feel<br>19.cost<br><span>20.come:0</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "1. I know if he always glance at me<br>2. I write a story every sunday<br>3. He cuts his hair every one month<br>4.She drive car with her friends every sunday morning<br>5. The children drinks a glass of milk every day<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "5-kalimat-verbal-dalam-bahasa-inggris-610",
            "question": "5\u00a0kalimat verbal dalam\u00a0bahasa inggris?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "We play football every morning<br>I go to the market every sunday<br>She plays soccer with Ella<br>He goes to the library<br>She buys some books in the store<br>Semoga Membantu<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-dialog-dengan-menggunakan-ungkapan-expression-love-and-sa-467",
            "question": "Buatlah dialog dengan menggunakan ungkapan expression love and sadness beserta situasinya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>\n<span>Me\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Mom, i should tell you right now</span></span>\n<br><span>\nMom : What is it\ndear ? tell me right now</span>\n<br><span>\n<span>Me\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : I should go to australia mom, i get that\nschollarship from school</span></span>\n<br><span>\nMom : Are you\nkidding me ?</span><br>\u00a0<span><span>Me\u00a0 : No mom, i\u2019m seriously this is a special\nchance for me to catch my dream would you like to </span></span>\n<span>\n<span>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 let me go ?</span></span><br>\u00a0<span><span>mom : But i\nlove you dear how can i let you go ?</span></span>\n<span>\n<span><br>me\u00a0\u00a0 : Calmdown mom everythings gonna be alright</span></span>\n<span>\n<span><br>mom : But ,\ni\u2019m afraid if i\u2019ll miss you my daughter i feel so sad\u00a0 if i let you go</span></span><br>\u00a0<span><span>me\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : It\u2019s ok mom, you can call me or message\nme distance is not a big problem</span></span><br>\u00a0<span>mom : If that\u2019s\nyou want i\u2019ll let you go, but you must take care there</span><br>\u00a0<span><span>me\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Sure mom\u00a0\nwish me luck</span></span> <span><br>mom : Sure dear</span><span><br><br></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "A : hy...<br>B : hy..<br>A : let&#039;s go to the cinema<br>B : what to do?<br>A : watching movies, now there recent a movie. you know?<br>B : really?? what the movie?<br>A : Harry Poter<br>B : really?? i love that movie. but.....<br>A : why??<br>B : i certainly shouldn&#039;t watch that movie<br>A : why?<br>B : now, i have a lot of tasks. so i will not go.<br>A : no problem. you can watch the next time<br>B : iam so sadness<br>A : be poison<br>B : thank you<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-text-spoof-pake-twist-falling-into-a-well-dong-306",
            "question": "Contoh text SPOOF pake twist \"falling into a well\" dong :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>\nSpoof text: Falling Into a Well</span>\n<span>\n</span>\n\nThere was a man. When he was walking, he fell into a well.\n<span>\n<br></span>\n\nMany people saw the incident so they came to save him. Unfortunately no \none could enter the well to bring him out. Later, a smart man came up \nwith a bright idea to throw the man a strong rope to try to pull him out\n the well.\n<span>\n<br></span>\n\nWhen the rope reached\u00a0 and hit the man\u2019s head, he shouted angrily: \u201cDon&#039; bother me! Pick your own well, I am bathing.\u201d\n<br>\n\nDo you get the point why that short passage can be labeled as a spoof \ntext? Before we are going to go further, Let&#039;s see its rough translation\n to help you to\u00a0 get better understanding\n<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "coba-sebeutkan-contoh-dari-spoof-dan-kesimpulannya-845",
            "question": "Coba sebeutkan contoh dari spoof dan kesimpulannya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Contoh :<br>Joe&#039;s Mother got angry because her son got a low mark on English test.<br>\n\"Why did you get such a low mark on that test?\" Asked mother angrily. \nAsked by his angry mother, Joe just kept silent and went out.<br>\nA few moment, Joe came back home and met his mother again. His mother asked the same question.<br>\nJoe answered steadily, \"Because of absence.\"<br>\n\"You mean you were absent on the day of the test?\" Mother wondered.<br>\nJoe replied, \"No, but the kid who sits next to me was.\"\n\n<br><br>Kesimpulan :<br><span><span>sebuah teks yang berisi tentang humor meski sebagian teksnya \nsudah dimodifikasi dari aslinya.</span></span><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "sebutkan-kata-sifat-dari-pengelompokan-tersebut-sebanyak-banyak-851",
            "question": "Sebutkan kata sifat dari pengelompokan tersebut! (sebanyak-banyaknya)    menurut:1.Skin (Cool, Ho, ...)\r\n\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 2. Place (in,at,on,\u00a0...)\r\n\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 3. Age (New,old,\u00a0...)\r\n\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 4. Nose (sweet, smelling, ...)\r\n\r\nTolong kerjasamanya Friend's.. thanks so'much!",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Skin = cool, hot, soft, dirty, clean, rude, ugly, beautiful\nPlace : in, on, at, beside, behind, in front, between.\nAge : old, young, new,",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}